Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, records
1862-2015
RU 212
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
27.25
The records consist of subject files, registers, annual reports, account books, scrapbooks, and letterpress books documenting the operations and activities of the Yale Graduate School of Arts and Sciences.
Yale University. Graduate School
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 25-A (YRG 25-A), Central records and records of the dean of the Yale Graduate School.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Biographical / Historical
The Yale Graduate School is one of the twelve schools comprising Yale University, and is the only one which awards the Ph.D. The Graduate School (called the Department of Philosophy and the Arts until 1892) was established in 1847 by an act of the Yale Corporation. In 1861, the Graduate School awarded the first Ph.D. degrees. For nine years following, Yale remained the only American university to award the Ph.D. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences was formally established in 1892 with the appointment of Arthur Twining Hadley as its first dean. In the same year, women were first admitted as candidates for the Ph.D. In 1919, the Yale Corporation placed the Master of Science degree under the jurisdiction of the Graduate School. In 1933, this degree was transferred to the several professional schools at Yale. In 1966, the Master of Philosophy Degree was first awarded.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of subject files, registers, annual reports, account books, scrapbooks, and letterpress books documenting the operations and activities of the Yale Graduate School of Arts and Sciences.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Graduate Students; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Graduate work; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Graduate work; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Graduate School
- Report of the Teaching Appointments Secretary, 1941; Accession 19ND-A-489
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Report of the Teaching Appointments Secretary, 1941 (Box 1)
- Graduate department register, 1895-1902; Accession 1938-A-002
  - Graduate department register, 1895-1902 (Box 1)
- Account books, scrapbooks, and letterpress books, 1862, 1897-1929; Accession 1992-A-023
  - Account book, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Letter press books
    - 1897 Oct - 1898 Jan (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1898 Jan - May (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1898 May -1899 Feb (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1899 Feb - Dec (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1899 Dec - 1900 Oct (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1900 Oct - 1902 May (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 1902 May - Jul (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 1903-1904 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 1904-1905 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 1904-1910 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 1905-1906 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 1906-1907 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 1907-1908 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - 1908-1909 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 1909-1910 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - 1910-1911 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Loomis fellowship scrapbook, 1902 May - 1917 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook with pictures of Europe (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Engineering at Yale, 1919-1920 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Graduate school scrapbook, 1919-1929 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Annual reports for the fiscal years 1992-1994, 1991-1994; Accession 1996-A-055
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2029
  - Annual reports, 1992-1994 (Box 1)
- Administrative records of the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, circa 1895-1950; Accession 2001-A-032
  - 3 bound journals containing minutes, policies, correspondence, etc., circa 1895-1950 (Box 1)
- Records of Deborah Thomas and David Spadafora as associate deans, circa 1968-1987; Accession 2004-A-059
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  - Records of David Spadafora
    - Committee Meetings
      - General, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - December Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - May Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - General, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - December Meeting, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - May Meeting, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - National Science Fellowships
      - National Needs Graduate Traineeship Program (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Graduate Fellowships (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Declarations, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - HGS Building Information (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - HGS (Resident) (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - HGS Dining Hall (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - HGS General Information (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - HGS Social Committee Agency Account, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - HHH Letters of Recognition (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Admissions Offers, 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Admissions, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Admissions, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Admissions, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - HGS Letters of Recognition, 1968-1987 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - HGS Expenses, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - 276/254 Prospect Street, 1972-1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - African Studies Fellowships, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - African Studies, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - African Studies Fellowships, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - African Studies, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - African Studies, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Non Graduate School EPH Thesis Directors (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - HGS-HHH Integration, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Grievances Procedure, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Councils of Graduate Schools (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Graduate School Senate Minutes, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Graduate Professional Student Senate and Center Finances, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Housing Survey Info (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Astronomy Current and Previous A/Y (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Biology Current and Previous A/Y (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Grant Notices and Applications (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - TF and AR Appointments, 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Sciences Admissions General Info, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Training Grants (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Student Evaluations, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Student Evaluations, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - General Information and Processing (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - Casual Payroll Science Department Reports (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - HERTZ Foundation (Sciences Applied To Human Problems) (Box 3, Folder 50)
      - Graduate Senate Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 51)
      - Graduate School Senate (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - Graduate Student Center, 1969-1977 (Box 3, Folder 53)
      - Housing Department (Box 3, Folder 54)
      - Budget, Grad School FSP for, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - Biology Department Support Plan (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - Fulbright C.I.E.S. (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Fulbright Hays
      - Insurance, 1974-1985 (Box 4, Folder 58)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 59)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 60)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 61)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 62)
      - Faculty, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 63)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Employment survey
      - Employment of Yale Ph.D.s (Box 4, Folder 68)
      - Employment Study Returns
        - 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 69)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 70)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 71)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 72)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 73)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 74)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 75)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 76)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 77)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 78)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 79)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Records of Deborah Thomas
    - Minority files
      - Minority Recruitment (Box 5, Folder 81)
      - Minority and Women Data (Box 5, Folder 82)
      - Singer Report, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 83)
      - Survey of Black Students, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 84)
      - ETS Graduate Minority Enrollment, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 85)
      - Black Faculty, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 86)
      - Job Opportunities for Minority Students (Box 5, Folder 87)
      - Black Graduate Students' Union, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 88)
      - Recruitment Trip, 1973 May 21 - June 1 (Box 5, Folder 89)
      - Minority Enrollment Figures Dwarfs and Elsewhere (Box 5, Folder 90)
      - Minority Recruitment, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 91)
      - Recruitment Ideas for, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 92)
      - Financial Assistance (Minorities) (Box 5, Folder 93)
      - Fellowships-Danforth Post-Grad Black Studies (Box 5, Folder 94)
      - Minority Recruitment, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 95)
      - Hampton Institute, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 96)
      - Morgan State Univ., 1979 October 22 (Box 5, Folder 97)
      - Atlanta University, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 98)
      - Minority Applicants, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 99)
      - Fisk University, 1979 October 15-16 (Box 5, Folder 100)
      - Hampton Institute, 1979 October 24 (Box 5, Folder 101)
      - Minority Advisory Council, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 102)
      - Minority Enrollment, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 103)
      - Minority Graduate Student Locater Service, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 104)
      - Eastern Consortium Cambridge, 1979 October 13 (Box 5, Folder 105)
      - Eastern Consortium Fipse Proposal, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Dept. files
      - Eastern Consortium Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 107)
      - Eastern Consortium, 1980 June 12-13 (Box 6, Folder 108)
      - University of D.C., 1979 October 22 (Box 6, Folder 109)
      - Eastern Consortium, Atlanta/ Washington, 1980 April 10-12 (Box 6, Folder 110)
      - Minority Offers for Admission, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 111)
      - American Indian Science and Engineering Society (Box 6, Folder 112)
      - Atlanta University, 1979 October 26 (Box 6, Folder 113)
      - Statistics, 1970-1976 (Box 6, Folder 114)
      - Sociology, 1970-1977 (Box 6, Folder 115)
      - Psychology, 1969-1977 (Box 6, Folder 116)
      - Russian, 1970-1977 (Box 6, Folder 117)
      - Operations Research, 1980-1986 (Box 6, Folder 118)
      - Organizational Behavior, 1981-1986 (Box 6, Folder 119)
      - International Relations, 1977-1986 (Box 6, Folder 120)
      - Economic History, 1980-1984 (Box 6, Folder 121)
      - I.D.P., 1977-1986 (Box 6, Folder 122)
      - East Asian Studies, 1977-1986 (Box 6, Folder 123)
      - Economics, 1981-1986 (Box 6, Folder 124)
      - Robert Bunselmeyer Minority Advisory Council (Box 7, Folder 125)
      - Afro-American Studies, 1977-1986 (Box 7, Folder 126)
      - Archeology, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 127)
      - Anthropology, 1977-1986 (Box 7, Folder 128)
      - Withdrawals, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 129)
      - Sociology, 1977-1986 (Box 7, Folder 130)
      - Statistics, 1977-1985 (Box 7, Folder 131)
      - Psychology Support Pattern, 1981-1986 (Box 7, Folder 132)
      - Russian, 1977-1986 (Box 7, Folder 133)
      - International Relations, 1967-1977 (Box 8, Folder 134)
      - Political Science, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 135)
      - Economics, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 136)
      - Political Science, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 137)
      - Economics, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 138)
      - East Asian Studies, 1972-1977 (Box 8, Folder 139)
      - Economics, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 140)
      - Anthropology, 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 141)
      - Anthropology, 1968-1977 (Box 8, Folder 142)
      - Misc. Outdated Correspondence, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 143)
      - Administrative Sciences, 1967-1980 (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - Minority files
      - Minority Recruitment, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 145)
      - Applicants Successful and Special, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 146)
      - Afro-American Cultural Center, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 147)
      - Atlanta University, 1976 October 22 (Box 9, Folder 148)
      - Baraboo Conference, 1976 August 1-3 (Box 9, Folder 149)
      - Chicano Proposal, Fall 1976 (Box 9, Folder 151)
      - Departmental Correspondence With Minority Applicants, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 153)
      - Fisk University, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 154)
      - Danforth Minority, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 155)
      - Follow Up Letters, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 156)
      - Ford Fsp. Chicano P.R. and American Indian, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 157)
      - Hampton Institute, 1976 October 13 (Box 9, Folder 158)
      - H.E.O.P, 1976 November 19 (Box 9, Folder 159)
      - Invitation to Recruit Declined, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 160)
      - Letter to 1st Year Minority Students (Box 9, Folder 161)
      - Minority Advisors, Placement Offices, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 162)
      - Minority Alums (Box 9, Folder 163)
      - Minority Correspondence No Reply, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 164)
      - Minority Seniors Exchange, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 165)
      - Ohio State Minority Recruitment, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 166)
      - Prospective Applicants for, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 167)
      - Summer Bio Program (Box 9, Folder 168)
      - Lincoln University, 1976 October 27 (Box 9, Folder 169)
      - LINKS Fin. Aid for Black Women Grads Bstn. (Box 9, Folder 170)
      - Minority Graduate Student Locater Service, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 171)
      - Summer Term Minority, 1974-1977 (Box 9, Folder 172)
      - Title IX Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 173)
      - U.C.L.A., 1976 (Box 9, Folder 174)
      - University of Florida April, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 175)
      - University of Texas Health Center at Dallas (Box 9, Folder 176)
      - Women's Colleges (Box 9, Folder 177)
      - Atlanta University, 1975 October 13-17 (Box 9, Folder 178)
      - Minority Recruitment, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 179)
      - Beringer, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 180)
      - Chicago and Michigan, 1975 October 27-29 (Box 9, Folder 183)
      - Chicano Applicants, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 184)
      - College Placement Services, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 186)
      - Committee on Racial Understanding (Box 9, Folder 187)
      - Coop. Minority Recruitment and Admissions-Harvard, Yale, Princeton, etc. (Box 9, Folder 188)
      - CUNY Recruitment, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 189)
      - DuBois Fsp., 1976 (Box 9, Folder 190)
      - Bud Duvall--Northwestern and Chicago Early, 1976 December (Box 9, Folder 191)
      - Economics Dept. Minority Proposal, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 192)
      - Ford Foundation Survey of Minority Support (Box 9, Folder 193)
      - GPSOMS Data Collection Forms (Box 9, Folder 195)
      - M.L. King Jr. Fsp., 1975 (Box 9, Folder 196)
      - A. Madrid, 1975 October 8-9 (Box 9, Folder 197)
      - Minority Application Stencil Draft (Box 9, Folder 198)
      - MGSLS, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 199)
      - Minority Students in Yale College, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 200)
      - Moton Center, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 201)
      - Va., Md. Morgan, 1975 October 6-8 (Box 9, Folder 202)
      - Names Submitted by Graduate Students (Box 9, Folder 203)
      - National Consortium for Black Professional Development, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 204)
      - Report and Exhortation DGS's, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 205)
      - Rosenberg (funding Minority proposals), 1976 (Box 9, Folder 206)
      - Tougaloo College, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 207)
      - U of TX Career Conference, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 208)
      - Minority Recruitment, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 209)
      - ASPIRA, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 210)
      - American Indian Recruitment, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 211)
      - Amos Visit, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 212)
      - Atlanta, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 216)
      - Berkeley Minority Programs Math and Zoo, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 217)
      - Black Alliance Conference Meade, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 218)
      - Chicano Applicants, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 219)
      - Compton Administration, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 220)
      - Howard University, 1982 October 28 (Box 10, Folder 221)
      - Minority Graduate Student Locater Service, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 222)
      - Minority Recruitment, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 223)
      - Atlanta University, 1982 October 26 (Box 10, Folder 224)
      - California, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 225)
      - Howard University, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 226)
      - Princeton, 1983 October 3-8 (Box 10, Folder 227)
      - Puerto Rico, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 228)
      - Nashville/ Atlanta, 1983 October 12-13 (Box 10, Folder 229)
      - CUNY, 1983 November 17 (Box 10, Folder 230)
      - Eastern Consortium, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 231)
      - Princeton, 1978 April 17 (Box 10, Folder 232)
      - Minority Graduate Student Locater Service, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 233)
      - Women in Science (Donner), 1978 January 20 (Box 10, Folder 237)
      - Minority Consortium Dwarfs and others, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 238)
      - Minority Seniors Exchange, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 239)
      - Hampton Institute, 1977 October 19 (Box 10, Folder 240)
      - Howard University, 1977 October 27 (Box 10, Folder 241)
      - Hunter College Site Conference, 1977 November 2 (Box 10, Folder 242)
      - The U of MI, 1977 November 7 (Box 10, Folder 243)
      - Princeton, 1980 September 24-25 (Box 10, Folder 244)
      - Queens College, 1980 December 11 (Box 10, Folder 245)
      - Recruitment, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 246)
      - Smith College, 1980 November 12 (Box 10, Folder 247)
      - Compton Administration, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 248)
      - CUNY Open House, 1981 November 12-13 (Box 10, Folder 249)
      - Atlanta University, 1981 October 23 (Box 10, Folder 250)
      - Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 251)
      - California, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 252)
      - MAC, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 253)
      - MGSLS, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 254)
      - Name Exchange, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 255)
      - Recruitment, Fall 1982 (Box 11, Folder 256)
      - Offers for Admission, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 257)
      - Minority Student Print-outs (Box 11, Folder 258)
      - Minority Enrollment, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 259)
      - Fisk University, 1982 October 18-19 (Box 11, Folder 260)
      - Responses to CMSGPS Report, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 261)
      - Tally Sheets and Print-outs, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 262)
      - Sloan Final Report, 1979 December 17 (Box 11, Folder 263)
      - University of Mississippi, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 264)
      - CSMSGPS Report Drafts (Box 11, Folder 265)
      - University of Texas, Austin (Box 11, Folder 267)
      - D.C. Area Schools, 1980 October 21-22 (Box 11, Folder 268)
      - MGSLS, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 269)
      - Berkley Stanford (Box 11, Folder 270)
      - Princeton, 1981 October 1-2 (Box 11, Folder 271)
      - Recruitment, Fall 1981 (Box 11, Folder 272)
- Records of the graduate school's foundation funds and fellowships, circa 1955-1965; Accession 2004-A-179
  - George F. Kutler Foundation for Microfilm Equipment (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Donald R. McLennan Jr. Fellowship (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Leigh Page Memorial Prize (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lafayette B. Mendel Fellowship in Biochemistry (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Henry and Lucy Moses Fund, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Mosler Safe Company Fellowship (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - National Distillers Products Corporation (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Edward J. Noble Foundation (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Louis M. Rabinowitz Fellowship in Economics (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Atomic Development Mutual Fund (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories Fellowship (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Connecticut Society of the Colonial Dames Scholarship (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Eastman Kodak Company Fellowship (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - French Department Fellowships (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Registration materials, 1926-1952; Accession 2005-A-049
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2028
  - 1926-1927 (Box 1)
  - 1927-1928 (Box 1)
  - 1928-1929 (Box 1)
  - 1929-1930 (Box 1)
  - 1930-1931 (Box 1)
  - 1931-1932 (Box 1)
  - 1932-1933 (Box 1)
  - 1933-1934 (Box 1)
  - 1934-1935 (Box 1)
  - 1935-1936 (Box 1)
  - 1936-1937 (Box 1)
  - 1937-1938 (Box 1)
  - 1938-1939 (Box 1)
  - 1939-1940 (Box 1)
  - 1940-1941 (Box 1)
  - 1941-1942 (Box 1)
  - 1942-1943 (Box 1)
  - 1943-1944 (Box 1)
  - 1944-1945 (Box 1)
  - 1945-1946 (Box 2)
  - 1946-1947 (Box 2)
  - 1947-1948 (Box 2)
  - 1948-1949 (Box 2)
  - 1949-1950 (Box 2)
  - 1950-1951 (Box 2)
  - 1951-1952 (Box 2)
  - 1952-1953 (Box 2)
  - 1953-1954 (Box 2)
- List of degree candidates, circa 1973-1974; Accession 2006-A-070 (Box 1)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2050
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.
- Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Teaching Fellows Program files, 1975-2015; Accession 2016-A-072
  Restricted until January 1, 2051
  - Enrollments Fall 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Enrollments Spring 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Enrollments Fall 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Enrollments Spring 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Enrollments Fall 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Enrollments 1992-93, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Enrollments 1991-92, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Enrollments Spring 1989-90, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Enrollments Fall 1989-90, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Student Enrollments 90/91-00/01, 1990-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - FAS Course Enrollments 97/98 Pre-95-99 (1 of 4), 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - FAS Course Enrollments 97/98 Pre-95-99 (2 of 4), 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - FAS Course Enrollments 97/98 Pre-95-99 (3 of 4), 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - FAS Course Enrollments 97/98 Pre-95-99 (4 of 4), 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Enrollments Spring 2000 (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Enrollments Spring 2000 (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Enrollments 1999-2000 (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Enrollments 1999-2000 (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Enrollments Spring 1999 (1 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Enrollments Spring 1999 (2 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Enrollments Spring 1999 (3 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Enrollments 1998-1999 (1 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Enrollments 1998-1999 (2 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Enrollments 1998-1999 (3 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Enrollments 1998-1999 (4 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Enrollments 1997-98 (1 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Enrollments 1997-98 (2 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Enrollments 1997-98, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Enrollments Spring 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Enrollments Fall 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Enrollments 1995-96, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Dept. Teaching Statistics Book I (1 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Dept. Teaching Statistics Book I (2 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Dept. Teaching Statistics Book I (3 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Dept. Teaching Statistics Book II (1 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dept. Teaching Statistics Book II (2 of 2), 1995-1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - John Goldin Teaching Statistics 1995-96 (1 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - John Goldin Teaching Statistics 1995-96 (2 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - John Goldin Teaching Statistics 1996-97 (1 of 3), 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - John Goldin Teaching Statistics 1996-97 (2 of 3), 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - John Goldin Teaching Statistics 1996-97 (3 of 3), 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - John Goldin 10/16/1997 Statistics on Teaching (1 of 5), 1997 October 16 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - John Goldin 10/16/1997 Statistics on Teaching (2 of 5), 1997 October 16 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - John Goldin 10/16/1997 Statistics on Teaching (3 of 5), 1997 October 16 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - John Goldin 10/16/1997 Statistics on Teaching (4 of 5), 1997 October 16 (Box 3, Folder 11)